chemicalelements.com 2010-11-21

# Chemical Elements.com - License and Privacy Statement

 Home

 About This Site  
 Comments  
 Help  
 Links  

 Window Version

 Show Table With:  
   Name  
   Atomic Number  
   Atomic Mass  
   Electron Configuration  
   Number of Neutrons  
   Melting Point  
   Boiling Point  
   Date of Discovery  
   Crystal Structure  

 Element Groups:  
   Alkali Metals  
   Alkaline Earth Metals  
   Transition Metals  
   Other Metals  
   Metalloids  
   Non-Metals  
   Halogens  
   Noble Gases  
   Rare Earth Elements  

|    | 

This site's license is rather simple, and is not written in words that only lawyers can understand. Please do not violate any of the items of this license.

  * **Privacy Statement**  
ChemicalElements.com respects its visitors' privacy. The site never asks for identifying information. Logs are used only to gather general information regarding visitors, not specific information used to identify users of the site. Any information that is gathered will never be sold, rented, loaned or traded with a third party. Participants in the ChemicalElements.com survey are encouraged to read [its privacy statement](http://www.swiftinteractive.com/Privacy/PrivacyStatement.html). If you have any questions regarding the site's privacy policy, please feel free to e-mail ChemicalElements.com. 
  * **Privacy Considerations from Ads**  
ChemicalElements.com uses advertising to support the costs of running the site. Some advertisers, advertising agencies, and other third parties that we contract with may place or read a "cookie," or a small bit of information, on your browser, to help collect information in the course of serving advertisements on the site. This is very common across the Internet, and does not cause concern for most users. If you are nevertheless concerned about cookies, please search for information on disabling cookies. Note that this may limit your use of many websites, although it should not affect your experience at ChemicalElements.com. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Some ads on this site are served by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

  * **Copying, Republishing, Mirroring**  
Please do not republish this site without permission. If you would like permission to do so, please e-mail me. 
  * **Printing**  
Feel free to print any part of this site. As long as you do not republish the site, in whole or in part, I have absolutely no problem with printing the site. 
  * **Linking**  
Feel free to link to any part of the site. If you are linking to the site as a whole, please use [http://www.chemicalelements.com](http://www.chemicalelements.com/) as the link URL. It is not necessary to e-mail me if you would like to link to the site. 
  * **Downloading**  
If you would like to download the site to your PC or for use on a school LAN in order to increase speed, please feel free to do so. However, I do ask you to make sure the site is not available over the web to the general public. 
  * **Using this site for illegal purposes**  
I cannot be held responsible for any unlawful use of this site. 
  * **Accuracy**  
I always try to make sure this site does not contain any inaccurate information. However, this is an impossible task. If you spot an error, please let me know. Meanwhile, I will continue to try to verify the information on the site. Please understand that I cannot be held responsible for any inaccurate information on this site. 
  * **Publicity**  
If you decide to give this site an award, or publish its URL in newspapers, television, magazines, etc., please e-mail me and let me know. Thanks! 
  * **Other**  
If you have any other questions about proper use of this site, feel free to e-mail me.
